<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>UACCB Career Coach — Latest Jobs</title>
    <link>https://uaccb.lightcastcc.com/work-opportunities?radius=40 miles&region=Batesville Campus</link>
    <description>The seven most recent job postings near UACCB (Career Coach).</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 16:36:37 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>30</ttl>
    <atom:link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/scott-phillips-UACCB/career-coach/main/uaccb-jobs.xml"/>
    <item>
      <title>Housing Program Specialist (substitute)</title>
      <link>https://ourhouseshelter.bamboohr.com/careers/201?source=aWQ9MzU%3D</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">uaccb:7eaae417-d78b-4dfa-9c51-d96539b05655</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 07:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[Our House — Part-Time — Approved
Department: HousingReports to: Lead Housing Program SpecialistEmployment Type: In-Person, Substitute, Hourly, Non-ExemptSchedule:On-Call SubstituteAbout Our HouseOur House empowers homeless and near-homeless families and individuals to succeed in the workforce, in school, and in life through hard work, wise decision-making, and active participation in the community. The Our House team has defined a set of seven Guiding Principles that characterize our culture and that we intentionally seek to uphold: Hard Work, Wise Decision-Making, Community, Initiative, Integrity, Safety, and Heart.About the RoleYou will be the after-hours staff member on duty. It will be your responsibility to oversee our large, 24/7 residential facility, the entire campus, and all people on the campus, including residents, volunteers, and visitors. If an incident occurs anywhere on the campus, you will be the person responsible for handling the situation. You will have significant crisis management responsibilities and must maintain good work integrity and effective communication.
Closes: 09-30-2025]]></description>
      <category>Part-Time</category>
      <category>Our House</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Housing Program Specialist (full-time)</title>
      <link>https://ourhouseshelter.bamboohr.com/careers/202?source=aWQ9MzU%3D</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">uaccb:b97ef08e-fc88-43d8-9355-fec1434b59b4</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 07:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[Our House — Full-Time — Approved
Department: HousingReports to: Lead Housing Program SpecialistEmployment Type: In-Person, Full-Time, Hourly, Non-ExemptAvailable Schedules:Multiple shift optionsAbout Our HouseOur House empowers homeless and near-homeless families and individuals to succeed in the workforce, in school, and in life through hard work, wise decision-making, and active participation in the community.About the RoleYou will be the after-hours staff member on duty. It will be your responsibility to oversee our large, 24/7 residential facility, the entire campus, and all people on the campus, including residents, volunteers, and visitors. If an incident occurs anywhere on the campus, you will be the person responsible for handling the situation. You will have significant crisis management responsibilities and must maintain good work integrity and effective communication.
Closes: 09-30-2025]]></description>
      <category>Full-Time</category>
      <category>Our House</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Behavior Support Specialist</title>
      <link>https://ourhouseshelter.bamboohr.com/careers/206?source=aWQ9MzU%3D</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">uaccb:0e370d8c-16b9-4de3-af46-887869ff01a9</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 07:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[Our House — Full-Time — Approved
Department: Mental HealthReports to: Health + Wellness CoordinatorEmployment Type: In-Person, Full-Time, Salary, ExemptAbout Our HouseOur House empowers homeless and near-homeless families and individuals to succeed in the workforce, in school, and in life through hard work, wise decision-making, and active participation in the community.About the RoleYou will be responsible for integrating the two-generation approach into behavior support strategies and collaboratively developing holistic behavior plans that support both the child's and the family's needs. By taking a person-centered approach, you will build trust, offer meaningful support, and connect individuals to appropriate resources. You will collaborate with classroom teachers, youth program specialists, the mental health team, and families to provide trauma-informed intervention strategies that ensure children have access to and experience a safe and nurturing environment and foster resilience in their development.
Closes: 09-30-2025]]></description>
      <category>Full-Time</category>
      <category>Our House</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Behavior Coach AmeriCorps Member</title>
      <link>https://ourhouseshelter.bamboohr.com/careers/204?source=aWQ9MzU%3D</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">uaccb:d6a8cc2c-9b25-4f84-9320-0ec1c2264a34</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 07:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[Our House — Full-Time — Approved
Service Position Title and Type: Behavior Coach AmeriCorps Member (Three-Quarter-time, 1200 hours)Name and Address of Program: Our House, 302 E. Roosevelt Road, Little Rock, AR 72206Service Locations: Our HousePurposeOur House empowers homeless and near-homeless families and individuals to succeed in the workforce, in school, and in life through hard work, wise decision-making, and active participation in the community.Service Position SummaryThe Behavior Coach AmeriCorps Member will serve in Our House’s Children's Programs, called Bright Beginnings and Our Club. Bright Beginnings serves over 100 children ages 0–5, and Our Club serves up to 200 youth in grades Kindergarten–12th grade. The Behavior Coach AmeriCorps Member will provide behavioral intervention in problem-solving, self-regulation, impulse control, and empathy for children of all ages.
Closes: 09-29-2025]]></description>
      <category>Full-Time</category>
      <category>Our House</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Employment Coach AmeriCorps Member</title>
      <link>https://ourhouseshelter.bamboohr.com/careers/205?source=aWQ9MzU%3D</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">uaccb:d1a8db57-5bdb-402e-ae9e-0080593d8bab</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 07:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[Our House — Full-Time — Approved
Service Position Title and Type: Employment Coach AmeriCorps (Reduced half-time, 675 hours)Name and Address of Program: Our House, 302 E. Roosevelt Road, Little Rock, AR 72206Service Locations: Our HouseService Position SummaryThe Employment Coach AmeriCorps Member will serve in Our House’s Career Center, which works with over 3,000 adults each year through employment and training services, adult education, and resource navigation. The Employment Coach AmeriCorps Member will serve to expand employment and wrap-around services for clients.
Closes: 08-29-2025]]></description>
      <category>Full-Time</category>
      <category>Our House</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Community Relations Coordinator</title>
      <link>https://ourhouseshelter.bamboohr.com/careers/207?source=aWQ9MzU%3D</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">uaccb:53ecb9b7-0eca-40ff-93ce-c9c826ebee4e</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 07:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[Our House — Full-Time — Approved
Department: DevelopmentReports to: Marketing & Events ManagerEmployment Type: In-Person, Full-Time, Salary, ExemptAbout the RoleYou will be responsible for building and strengthening Our House’s relationships with the broader community, including donors, media partners, volunteers, and corporate supporters. You will lead outreach efforts, represent Our House at public events, coordinate press and media opportunities, and steward potential funders through the giving process.
Closes: 09-12-2025]]></description>
      <category>Full-Time</category>
      <category>Our House</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cashier</title>
      <link>https://uaccb.lightcastcc.com/posting/e0b64feb-8f3a-4676-a137-0de09bb6c7a4</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">uaccb:e0b64feb-8f3a-4676-a137-0de09bb6c7a4</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 07:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[Tripp Supply, Inc. — Full-Time — Approved
As a cashier, you’ll be the friendly face that greets customers, processes purchases efficiently, and helps ensure every customer leaves with a positive experience. You’ll also pitch in to keep the front of the store clean, organized, and running smoothly. We are open 6 days a week, Monday - Saturday. Our hours are M-F 7am-5:30pm, and Saturday 7:30am-4pm.Responsibilities:Greet customers and provide excellent customer serviceOperate the cash register and handle cash, credit, and debit transactionsAnswer basic customer inquiries and direct them to the right department or staff memberKeep the checkout area clean and organizedRestock impulse items and assist with light merchandising as neededCollaborate with other team members to ensure smooth daily operationsQualifications:Previous cashier or retail experience is a plus, but not required—we’re happy to train the right personFriendly, respectful, and dependableComfortable handling money and basic mathStrong communication and interpersonal skillsAbility to stand for extended periods and lift up to 25 lbsWhat We Offer:Supportive, family-style work environmentFlexible schedulingEmployee discounts on merchandiseOpportunities to learn about tools, hardware, and home improvement
Closes: 08-28-2025]]></description>
      <category>Full-Time</category>
      <category>Tripp Supply, Inc.</category>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>